Derek Bardini

970 306 9443

derekbardini@gmail.com

PO Box 7915 Avon, CO 81620

SUMMARY

Resident of Vail, Colorado since 2012, I have had a full and enjoyable life the greater part of the last decade. With a background in hospitality, food services, as well as transportation I have become excellent at working with people. In these uncertain times, I have decided to make a complete career change. I am now a Full Stack Web Developer. Available immediately.

SKILLS

CSS/Bootstrap/Foundation
javaScript, jQuery
Node

EXPERIENCE

Server, Matsuhisa

Vail, CO — 2015- 2020

- Coordinated custom meals worth well over \$10,000
- Learned what being a part of a high performing team
- Gained invaluable people skills
- Recieved multiple accolades through customer review

Night Audit Supervisor, Solaris Residences

Vail, CO — 2012-2016

- Started as a valet before working up to being a supervisor
- Increased building security, as well as integrity of guests' personal information by suggesting stricter policies at

EDUCATION

University of Minnesota— Coding Boot Camp, 2020-2021

Full Stack Developer

Richland College — Associate of Science, 2008- 2010

 Maintained B+ Average while working full time. front desk

- Provided valet and bell service, as well as front desk/ concierge services to guests
- Executed various clerical duties